You don't know, babe
When you hold me
And kiss me slowly
It's the sweetest thing
And it don't change
If I had it my way
You would know that you are
You're the coffee that I need in the morning
You're my sunshine in the rain when it's pouring
Won't you give yourself to me?
Give it all
I just wanna see
How beautiful you are
You know that I see it
I know you're a star
Where you go I'll follow
No matter how far
If life is a movie
You know you're the best part
You're the best part
You're the one that I desire
When we wake up
And then we make love
It makes me feel so nice
You're my water when I'm stuck in the desert
You're the talent all I take when my head hurts
You're the sunshine of my life
I just wanna see how beautiful you are
You know that I see it, I know you're a star
Where you go I'll follow, no matter how far
If life is a movie then you're the best part
Oh, you're the best part
Oh, best part
If you love me won't you say something
If you love me won't you
Love me won't you
If you love me, won't ya
Ah If you love me, won't ya
Say something
If you love me, won't ya
I will just
Ah, ah, ah, ah